Huh? Amazing, right?
- Yeah.
- Bathroom.
Bedrooms.
Nice.
Views of other
bedrooms and bathrooms.
I really appreciate you
letting me crash here, bud.
Are you kidding?
You're doing us a favor.
No flush Tony
just moved out last week.
You're sure this
isn't a problem?
Seriously, the best day
of my life
was when I heard you got
traded to the rangers.
You're family. My place
is your place, man.
Technically, it's my place.
Okay, and next time I say,
"hey, let me
help you with that,"
let's try
"no thanks, I got it."
You look like an eater.
So, just so we're clear,
the left side
of the fridge is mine.
( Knocks on door )
I got it.
Tucker, come on.
My brother
and my best friend--
It's never gonna get
any better than this.
The three of us together,
there's nothing
that's gonna stop us.
Except for maybe that.
There's a baby on my doormat.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
♪ it's amazing how
the unexpected ♪
♪ can take your life
and change directions. ♪
where did it come from?
Danny: I don't know.
But whoever left it,
they couldn't have gotten far.
Stay there, baby.
Make sure she stays there!
I'm just saying,
for a woman who
just had a baby,
she moves remarkably fast.
How could she just
leave her here?
Ben, you gotta calm down, okay?
I'm sure she's not even
your baby.
Exactly, it could
just as easily
be your baby, right?
Not so much, no.
And I've only been
in town an hour.
I mean, I'm fast, but...
I'm not that fast.
This is not my baby.
Wait, wait, wait!
Guys, we got a note.
Her name's Emma.
I don't know any Emmas.
The baby's name is Emma.
Hi, Emma.
Hey, Ben.
Did I ever tell you
about that hot waitress
I went out with named Emma?
Danny, focus!
The mother.
- Oh, yeah.
- Who's the mother?
Sorry, um,
Angela.
Ben and Tucker: Angela!
- Of course.
- That's right.
Who is Angela?
She was nice. Actress.
That girl was crazy.
Does it say anything else?
Uh, she's sorry.
She didn't know
what else to do.
And she just needs
a little time.
Time? How much time?!
( Knocks on door )
And that would be
the perfect amount of time.
Oh.
That's Riley.
I gave her a call
while you were outside.
Riley?
Fatpants Perrin?
What's she doing here?
You have a friend
named Fatpants?
Oh, I'm definitely
marking my food.
No.
Riley's in law school now.
It took her a while.
I guess the LSAT's
kind of tricky,
but trust me, she will
know what to do.
Ri-Gantor?
Ben-wetter!
Look at you.
You look amazing.
How did that happen?
I may have lost a pound or two.
Hundred.
You sat on my head and gave me
a concussion, remember?
Tuck, Riley.
Riley, Tucker.
Hi.
Riley grew up across
the street from us
and used to kick
the crap out of Ben
every day of his life.
Oh, and congrats
on the law school thing.
- Thanks.
- Don't worry--I know a bunch
of people that had
a hard time getting in.
- Ow, ow, ow, ow!
- Why did you tell him that?
( Baby cries )
I didn't do anything.
Oh.
Hey.
Hey, it's okay, princess.
Aren't you gonna pick her up?
Me?
What, you guys see breasts
and instantly think mommy?
( Chuckling )
Okay, fine.
Hi.
Okay.
Come here, angel.
Oh.
( Chuckles )
Hi.
Believe me,
I know how scary it is
to wake up
in a strange place.
I'm just making conversation.
Are you hungry?
I bet you're hungry, huh?
Let's see
what you got--
Is this all you
brought with you?
Oh, well, that's okay.
We'll just send
one of these boys out
for provisions and--
Oh...
I think somebody
needs her diaper changed.
I'll go to the store.
Yeah, I'm going, too.
No.
( Grunts )
Boys are so stupid,
aren't they?
Yes, they are.
They're so stupid.
All right, so then you just
stick the tabs down,
and voila,
she's good to go.
Oh.
Hold her while
I get her bottle ready,
- would you?
- Uh, me?
I'm not really a baby person.
Hold her.
( Murmurs )
Whee!
Isn't this fun?
There you go.
All right.
Want to maybe, uh,
take a step over here?
Is she okay?
Uh-huh.
Have a seat.
Oh.
Nice and easy.
Ah.
Is she having fun?
Yeah.
You guys look comfy.
I can't believe
this is happening.
I'm not ready to be a dad.
What if Angela
never comes back?
Oh, my God, taste this.
Yo.
Chicken, carrots, and pasta.
Okay?
All in this little jar.
( Laughs )
It's like, gross,
yet oddly delicious.
( Mouths word )
Come on, man.
It's gonna be okay.
How do you know?
I don't, but it's all I got.
Excuse me,
how old is your baby?
Oh, um...
That's a good question.
I met Angela at that
party in the village...
- Mm.
- And we dated for maybe six weeks
before we were...
Intimate.
And she broke up with me
pretty much right after that.
I'm sure there was
no correlation.
So, we're into August now,
and they take,
like, nine months
once they're up and running.
I think so.
So...
( Sighs )
Three months.
Three months!
My baby's three months old.
Mm-mm.
- Put this back.
- What?
She ain't got no teeth.
Put it back.
( Softly murmurs )
So, the first thing
Ben has to do
is take a paternity test.
( Mouths words )
我想说
很明显 这就是他的孩子
一样的笑容
一模一样的耳朵
连眼球上 长的那个闪亮的小斑点
都是一样的
怎么啦？
我鼻子上有什么东西吗
我就知道你们觉得这样很可笑
但是一点都不
你居然喜欢Ben
什么
怎么可能 听起来太疯狂了
我一直都喜欢戏弄他
天啊
你是真的喜欢Ben
我们回来咯
嘿 Ben 你肯定不会相信
刚刚我才发现Riley
所以你们买的怎么样了
你们刚一走
我才想到我应该
先给你们一张购物清单
为什么？我的意思是每个人都知道
你不应该给一个
还没有四个月大的婴儿买干粮
并且还希望她可以自己坐起来
刚刚那个女人还真是刻薄
我想我们把该做的都做完了
来吧
现在只要帮她拍拍背
让她打个嗝就好了
我想你肯定能做好的
什么 我吗 现在 别逗了
这里 tucker
-非常好，danny
-怎么啦？
-现在该你来管这个小家伙了
-等等
你不会现在走吧？
-对啊 我正打算走
-别走 我保证我会老实一点的
我刚刚已经跟你示范要怎么做了啊
对，可是我没认真看
你不能走
Ben 快让Riley留下来
-你不能走
-拜拜
哇哦 Ben
我可从来没注意
你的眼睛有多闪亮
拜托了 Riley
没有你 我们肯定熬不过今天晚上的
好吧
我留下来
看吧 这就是我正要说的
对吧  她没有吐奶在我的衣服上吧
没没，看起来很好
衣服完全跟新的一样 哥们
太好了
我5点应该回得来
等一下 你现在要去哪儿
我要去上班了
等等 你难道不能先找个人顶替一下吗
恩 好主意
但现在说太晚了
不 等一下 哥们
我和tuck是肯定不会帮你看孩子的
你哥哥说的很对
我想说没有...
喂
谢谢了老哥，再见
怎么又是这样
太棒了
谁说你一无是处的
应该是你吧
Riley 我现在到底该怎么办
说真的 在angela回来以前
我们也做不了什么
不过 我觉得我们得讨论一下
家里的那个小胖妞儿
就这一次不是用来形容我
你有想过以后怎么办吗
我真的不知道自己想要什么
去年 我在帮人家修房子
在那之前 我在餐厅当服务生
现在 我又成了个调酒师
我到现在都还没想清楚自己的生活
更何况我又不是你
什么意思
拜托
大学
法学院等等
你现在完全变了个人
你知道自己想要什么 而且你一直在为自己想要的努力
是啊
也不全是
冰块掉进我的胸罩里了
我真的很抱歉
以前一直骑你头上
Angela回去了
哥们 我现在离开一会儿
很抱歉总是挖苦你
慢慢来 大胖妞儿
加油
Angela现在在哪儿
首先我要说得是
她把孩子吵醒了
然后她要我给你那个信封
你让她走了
你吃错药了吧
不好意思
是我的错
但我当时在全神贯注地帮你照顾孩子
去看信吧 你肯定会开心的
全部都是领养申请
她准备让Emma接受领养
并且她想要我放弃Emma的抚养权
如果我签了 我就不用再当爸爸了
太好了 不是吗
看吧 我不是唯一一个
觉得兴奋的人
所以我签了以后
Emma就会有个新的爸爸对吗
差不多是这样
信上说
已经有家庭在等了
如果我签字了
让她走了
那我就不想再听到这件事了
永远也不想再谈论这件事了 好吗
-没问题
-好的
我的宝贝外孙在哪儿呢
妈 你来这儿干嘛
我当奶奶了
- 老妈
- 闪开
她来这儿干嘛
你跟她说孩子的事了
我甚至都没告诉她 我在你这
我待会再找你算账
你好
她真惹人爱啊
Yeah, I really don't 我真的不觉得你的笑带有爱
think that's love
that you're smelling.
现在谁来跟我解释一下
为什么我在做完指甲的时候
突然听到我当奶奶了
Jennifer Perrin迫不及待的想让我知道
自从她那个胖女儿进了法学院
她就开始变得...
你好啊Riley
我都没注意你在这儿
你现在好瘦啊
你应该挂个铃铛在身上
天啊
这是胶带吗
我们是要把她的尿布粘起来
你们居然找不到一个订书机
无语了
我现在不能签这些协议
我不会让这些事情发生
不要担心妈妈
你认为什么是对的你就去做
我百分百的支持你
什么协议
这是你自己的事咯 老弟
妈...
我有一些事情要告诉你
我知道 你们让一些女孩儿怀孕
是因为不知道
避孕的基本措施
这些就不用说了 好吗 亲爱的
Mrs. Wheeler?
Bonnie.
- Really?
- Mrs. Wheeler.
Emma's mom wants to put
Emma up for adoption emma的妈妈想让她被领养
and for Ben
to sign away his rights.并且希望ben签下协议放弃父亲的权利
Really?真的吗？
So you're-- 所以你是
you're thinking about
giving up this little girl?你正在打算放弃这这个小家伙是吗
Yeah, I was thinking about it.是的，我就是这么想的
Oh, good.哦太好了
( Sighing and laughing )
Good-- what do you
mean, good? 好？你所谓的好是什么意思？
Oh, Ben, honey.哦ben，亲爱的
You can't begin to understand 你不能理解当父母需要做多大的牺牲
the kind of sacrifice it takes
to be a parent.
When I married your father,当我嫁给你爸爸的时候
and I had you two,并且生了你们以后
I had to put my dreams on hold.我也不得不放弃我的梦想
- What dreams?什么梦想
- Being single and childless.当个单身并且没有孩子的女人
Ben...
Honey, I love you, 亲爱的，我爱你
but you can't raise
this little girl.
You haven't even finished
raising yourself.
You can't cook,
you're barely
paying your bills...
Honey, I still buy your pants.
This baby
needs a grown-up.
You gotta sign those papers.
9 am.
She'll be ready.
( Phone beeps )
Done.
Somebody from
the adoption agency
will be here first thing
in the morning.
You okay?
Yeah, why wouldn't I be?
Ben, if you don't
want to do this, man--
It doesn't matter.
Mom was right.
I couldn't raise this baby
even if I wanted to.
Bro, it's going to be okay.
It happened,
you dealt with it,
and now, like you said,
we're never talking
about this again.
I could have been a model.
But you've seen
your uncle Danny.
Yeah.
No body could
recover from that.
He was so big,
I had to have
a "c," "d," and "e" section.
No, don't.
I swear to God.
- Okay. Okay.
- No, I will hurt you.
Okay.
So...
Did you always like Ben?
Oh, my God, you're obsessed.
( Laughing )
I don't know.
Kind of.
Guess I always thought
maybe someday,
but back then I just figured
I was too fat,
or too--
loud, or too hairy, or--
Okay, we're not making a list.
Well, you've grown
to be a beautiful
and successful woman--
I think you can
safely move on
from Ben Wheeler.
Why would I want to do that?
Uh, did you miss
the part in the story
about the baby?
The baby he doesn't
want to give up?
If that's true, then why
did he make that call?
Because his entire family
is telling him he can't do it.
If nobody believes in him,
how can he believe in himself?
He can't do it alone.
You don't know that.
( Cell phone beeps )
Oh, it's Ben.
Your mom's about
to leave him alone
with the baby.
You're going?
"Alone" is in all caps.
Ow! Ow!
What was that for?
For making me
talk about my feelings.
You know I hate that.
And go easy on your brother,
okay?
He looks up to you.
In his eyes,
you have everything.
Not everything.
( Bell dings )
Wait, wait, wait!
- Wait.
- Oh, my God.
You-- you gotta
give me a minute.
( Panting )
Maybe now I know
why I was traded.
You were right.
I didn't believe in him.
I didn't think he could do it.
So why are you telling me?
Because...
If you go in there
and help him,
he'll never believe
in himself, either.
Riley, Riley,
Riley, Riley, please?
She's hungry,
or thirsty, or tired.
I don't know,
I don't speak baby.
( Elevator dings )
Tuck.
What is going on?
Vanessa and I
were at the movies
when Ben called and said
Emma's having
some kind of meltdown.
I don't think
Emma's the problem.
Tucker, I swear
if you're not home
in two seconds...
I'm gonna eat all your food.
Tucker?!
( Groans )
( Cell phone ringing )
Okay!
Turn it off!
( Cell phone
continues ringing )
( Emma murmurs )
Okay.
So, it looks like
it's just gonna be
you and me, huh?
Guess we're really
gonna do this thing.
Okay.
Okay, Emma, hi.
Hi, baby.
Come on, it's okay.
Please don't break,
please don't break,
please don't break.
Okay.
Okay. It's okay.
- It's okay.
- ( Emma cries )
It's okay.
It's okay, Emma.
Daddy's here.
It's okay.
( Yelps )
( Emma cries )
Aah.
It's okay.
I'm telling you,
there is no way.
Bodily functions
make him queasy.
He can do it.
Where's your faith, man.
See?
Here you go.
There.
Okay.
Hi. Hi.
Hi.
Emma?
( Sighs )
Please eat.
Come on, Emma.
Look, look, Emma, it's good.
It's good.
Mmm.
Oh, total lie.
It's actually quite disgusting.
No wonder you don't
want to eat.
Please eat.
Come on, Emma.
Just a sip, okay?
( Fusses )
Come on.
Okay, come on.
- ( Crying )
- Come on, you have to eat.
I'm begging you.
Come--
( fusses )
( Murmuring )
What?
You like that?
Look what daddy can do.
Huh?
I do this at work every day.
You want some now?
You want some?
Here it comes.
Here it comes, baby.
( Laughs )
Oh, my God, you're eating.
Thank you so much.
( Cries )
Holy crap,
now I'm crying.
( Chuckles )
Crap. Don't say crap.
Don't use swear words.
( Laughs )
Oh, I can't believe
you're eating.
( Chuckles )
You're so cute.
Hey, wake up.
Dude, you're drooling on me.
Oh.
Ahh...
Boo!
Ooh.
( Ben mimicking monkey )
Hey.
Hey. You okay?
Yeah.
I think I want to do this.
I can't let her go.
I love her.
Did you guys hear me?
Yeah.
Yeah, we heard you.
You should probably
call the agency.
It's almost 7:00.
Come on, mi amor.
Here we go.
Ooh, somebody could use a bath.
Oh. You both could.
I'm gonna go get a bottle ready.
But I want to give
it to her, okay?
We're really gonna have to get
on some kind of schedule though.
- For real.
- What do you mean?
Well, we have a
baby now so I mean,
we kind of have to be adults.
Ben: Okay. I'll do the shopping.
Tucker: Okay, but
let's talk about...
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com